# Maciej Sawicki

saw.maciej@gmail.com +48 696 022 099 maciejsawicki.com

## Summary

Senior UX/UI designer with more than 10 years of experience in SaaS products, both B2C and B2B. Expertise in User Centered Design methodology. Specializing in prototyping and user research for complex products. Conducted over 200 usability tests on own prototypes. Exceptional ability to find simple solutions for complex problems. Highly productive and always on time.

## **Experience**

**BugBug.io** • Full-time from March 2022 • 2 years part-time Product Designer

Espeo Software • 1 year (2021 - 2022) • Full-time Lead Product Designer

Rachuneo • 2 years (2019 - 2021) • Part-time 40% Product Designer

**Currency One •** 4 years (2017 - 2021) • Full-time UX Designer

**Egnyte** • 3 years (2014 - 2017) • Full-time UX Designer

**Blueberry Communication Group •** 2 yrs 4 mos (2012 - 2014) Head of Strategic Planning / UX Designer

#### Skills

Problem solving

••••

User research

••••

Prototyping

••••

Graphic design

••••

HTML/CSS

••••

JS/jQuery

••••

Workshops

## Languages

Polish (native)

••••

English (C1)

### **Education**

#### **SGH Warsaw School of Economics**

Master's degree in Management & Marketing Listed among the top 10% of students

## **Projects & Portfolio**

View portfolio presentation  $\rightarrow$ 

### **Tools**

Webflow

••••

Figma

UXPin

••••

AdobeXD

••••

Photoshop

••••

Google Analytics

JIRA

Ableton Live

••••

Logic Pro

••••

Google Analytics

••••

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in the application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process in accordance with Art. 6 paragraph 1 letter a of the Regulation of the European Parliament and of the Council (EU) 2016/679 of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).